<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">DAVdroid JB Workaround</string>
    <string name="label">DAVdroid JB Workaround</string>
    <string name="account_type">bitfire.at.davdroid</string>
    <string name="package_name">at.bitfire.davdroid</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">DAVdroid JB Workaround</string>
    <string name="jb_bug_workaround_app_package">at.bitfire.davdroid.jbworkaround</string>
    
    <string name="workaround_info_html"><![CDATA[
        <h1>DAVdroid Jelly Bean Workaround</h1>
        <p>Thank you for purchasing and thus supporting DAVdroid in Google Play Store.</p>
        
        <p>Unfortunately, there are two issues with paid Google Play apps:</p>

		<h2>1. Accounts may be gone after a reboot</h2>
		<p>You may encounter the problem that all your <strong>DAVdroid accounts (including contacts and events) are gone
        after rebooting your device</strong>. The reason is a <a href="https://code.google.com/p/android/issues/detail?id=34880">bug in Android</a>
        that causes accounts of paid apps to be removed on start-up because the (encrypted) APK files are
        loaded <i>after</i> checking for orphaned accounts.</p>
        <p>Affected users:<br/>
        * all Android 4.1 users who have got DAVdroid from Play Store;<br/>
        * Android 4.2 users who have got DAVdroid from Play Store only with certain devices (for instance, most Samsung devices)</p>
        
        <h2>2. Accounts may be gone after upgrading DAVdroid</h2>
        <p>You may encounter the problem that all your <strong>DAVdroid accounts (including contacts and events) when Play Store
        updates DAVdroid</strong>. The reason is <a href="https://code.google.com/p/android/issues/detail?id=66905">another bug in Android</a>
        that causes accounts of paid apps to be removed when upgrading for a similar reason.</p>
        <p>Affected users: some Android 4.4.2 users who have got DAVdroid from Play Store (known for Nexus devices and Moto G)</p>
        
        <h2>What to do?</h2>
        <p>This workaround is free, and the bug only affects paid (and therefore encrypted) apps. The workaround fakes a DAVdroid sync
        adapter so Android doesn\'t delete DAVdroid related data, neither after a reboot nor when upgrading.</p>
        
        <p>If you see red DAVdroid symbols in the settings, contacts or events, it means that the fake DAVdroid adapter is active.
        In this case, please wait a minute and try again. The workaround should load the real DAVdroid adapter and make the icons green.
        If it does not, you can try to launch the workaround manually and try again.</p>
        
        <p>Please see also <a href="http://davdroid.bitfire.at/faq?pk_campaign=jb-workaround-app">DAVdroid FAQ</a>.</p>
    ]]></string>
    
    <string name="davdroid_not_installed"><![CDATA[
        <h1>DAVdroid Jelly Bean Workaround</h1>
        
        <p>The only purpose of this app is to work around two bugs which only occur when using DAVdroid from PlayStore:</p>
        <p>* DAVdroid accounts may be gone after rebooting the device<br/>
        * DAVdroid accounts may be gone after upgrading DAVdroid to a new version</p>
        
        <h2>DAVdroid not found</h2>
        <p>It seems that DAVdroid is not installed on this device.</p>
        <p><b>There\'s no reason to keep this workaround app installed without DAVdroid.</b></p>
    ]]></string>
    
    <string name="davdroid_not_from_play_store"><![CDATA[
        <h1>DAVdroid Jelly Bean Workaround</h1>
        
        <p>The only purpose of this app is to work around two bugs which only occur when using DAVdroid from PlayStore:</p>
        <p>* DAVdroid accounts may be gone after rebooting the device<br/>
        * DAVdroid accounts may be gone after upgrading DAVdroid to a new version</p>
        
        <h2>DAVdroid not installed from Play Store</h2>
        <p>It seems that DAVdroid has been installed from %s.</p>
        <p>Because this workaround app is only required when using DAVdroid from Play Store,
        <b>there\'s no reason to keep this workaround app installed.</b></p>
    ]]></string>
    
    <string name="credits"><![CDATA[        
        <h2>Credits</h2>
        <p>This workaround uses code from <a href="https://github.com/dmfs/jb-workaround-template/">Marten Gajda\'s JB Workaround Template</a>
        (Apache License Version 2.0).</p>
    ]]></string>
    
    <string name="external_apk">an external APK file</string>
    <string name="get_davdroid">Get DAVdroid</string>
    <string name="uninstall_davdroid_jb_workaround">Uninstall DAVdroid JB Workaround</string>

</resources>